一道的Casey Alfonso/和二道的9次全国冠军 Tony Cooper
and nine-time national champion Tony Cooper
- 感觉怎么样/- 很好
- How do you feel?/- Great.
我紧张得肠子抽筋了
****
在赛前 你总是比我还紧张
your****
你还是不想去法学院?
You sure you don't wanna go to law school?
我痛恨律师
I hate lawyers.
我也是 去吧 宝贝
And so do I, go get him baby
准备
Ready to go.
让我们拭目以待吧
Let's hear it,folks!
Casey Alfonso领先不到半个车长
And it's casey alfonso by/less than half a car length!
完美的冲刺 英雄出少年
What a spectacular finish/for the young phenom.
Casey Alfonso完成惊人的冲线
Casey alfonso with an amazing finish.
最后关头你做了什么
What'd you do at the end there?
嗯
Yeah,heh...
250英尺的时候 车有点失控/但是开到半程
At about 250 feet,the car got out of/shape a bit.But about halfway down...
我进入状况
I just got into the zone or something.
把车控制在最佳状态/这是我赛车生涯中最酷的一次
I pedaled it back into the groove.It/was the coolest ride of my life!
击败9次全国冠军Tony Cooper
How does it feel to beat/nine-time national champion
是什么感觉
tony cooper?
抱歉 能再说一遍吗
I'm sorry.Can you repeat that?
击败9次全国冠军Tony Cooper
How does it feel to/beat nine-time national
是什么感觉?
champion tony cooper?
Casey Casey
Casey!Casey! Casey!
让开 Casey
Out of the way!Out of the way.Casey!
Casey!/Brian叫救护车
Casey! Get the/ambulance! Brian, get the ambulance!
Casey
Casey...
68岁男性 不吸烟
68-year-old/male,non-smoker.
68岁 多好的年纪
Ah,68's a good run.
上锁的箱子里留下不少好东西
That'll leave something in/the lockbox for the rest of us.
- 下一个/- 那是你的早餐?
- Next!/- That's your breakfast?
准确的说 是Wilson的午餐
Technically,it's Wilson's lunch.
- 20个月大的婴儿 持续皮疹 发烧/- 哭得太多
- 20-month-old baby,persistent/rash,fever... - Too much crying.
- 女大学生有.../- 太戏剧化了
- Female college student with.../- Too much drama.
你不会在乎哭闹和戏剧化
You don't care about/the crying or the drama.
因为你根本就不会去看病人
'cause you won't see the patient.
就算来了个老年病人/只要他鼻涕颜色够古怪 你也会愿意医他
And you'd treat methuselah if/his snot had an interesting color.
意味着你早就决定了要接哪份病历
It means you've already decided/which case you wanna take next.
说说高速赛车手
Tell me about speed racer.
女性 昏厥 听觉与视觉运作功能紊乱
Female,seizure with visual and/auditory processing deficiency.
- 我做了会诊/- 是哪种赛车
- I did a consult and/- What kind of race car?
短程加速赛车
Dragster.
- 继续/- 你就根据车型决定接不接病人?
- Continue./- You're gonna take a case based on the car she drives?
比航天飞机速度更快的赛车
Nothing says "thanks for saving my life"
赛车手说出"谢谢救了我的命"/一定美妙无匹
like a test drive in a car that/accelerates faster than the space shuttle.
她还没死 你救什么命
You can't save her/life,'cause she's not dying.
化验报告显示她有脱水迹象
Her lab shows signs of dehydration.
病因很有可能就是 中暑
That means the problem's/just likely...Heatstroke.
要在4秒半的时间内中暑/难度不小
Kinda hard to get/heat-struck in 41/2 seconds.
穿上三层防火服 情况就不同了
Not when you're wearing a/three-layer fireproof suit.
抱歉
Excuse me.
House医生?
Dr. House?
我不是 那懒虫又请病假了/我可以给他带个口讯
No,lazy ass called in sick/again.We can give him a message.
能私下谈谈吗
May we talk in private?
是中暑的话
So...either it's heatstroke,
我们下午就放大假了
in which case we take the afternoon off,
如果是别的/你们在两分钟之内给我诊断
or it's one of the diagnoses that you/guys are gonna have for me in two minutes.
- 你管事/- 我知道
- You're in charge./- I know.
- 警察/- 他没配枪
- Cop?/- He's not packing.
你爸爸不是警察就是保安
Your dad's either a/cop or a security guard.
或者她随身带着武器
Or she carries a weapon.
你是中情局的?
You're with the CIA?
我们有一名特工在执行任务时染病
One of our employees just/returned from an assignment sick.
他是暗杀计划的牺牲品
We believe he may be the victim/of an assassination attempt.
好 你要不要关上门
Sure.You wanna close the door?
门?
Door?
你是来跳脱衣舞的吧
Well,I assume you're gonna drop/trou at some point during the dance.
- 春光可别外泄 让别人看到/- 这不是玩笑
- I don't see why I should share./- This isn't a joke.
如果你愿意帮忙 现在就得走人
If you're willing to help/us,we need to leave now.
如果要我走去什么地方/至少要有五个小妞候着
If I have to walk somewhere,there/better be at least five girls involved.
她们最好为了上大学 不得不打工赚钱
And they better be working/their way through college.
想到些什么
Okay,what do you got?
遗传性大脑功能障碍 短暂性脑缺血
Hereditary brain/disorder,transient ischemia,
或者副肿瘤综合征
or paraneoplastic syndrome.
以上几项不会在静脉输液后就好转/是中暑
None of those go away with/iv fluids.It's heatstroke.
或者库欣综合征(皮质醇增多症)/或者缺钙
Or cushing's or calcium deficiency.
- 你这朋友是谁/- 他是我的"伴侣"
- Who's your friend?/- We use the term "life partner."
询问病史 做神经检查 大脑MRI
Get a fresh history,neurological/exam,and an mri of her head.
15分钟享受艳舞 半小时洗刷灵魂
15 minutes for the lap dance,a half/hour to scrub the guilt off my soul.
45分钟后见
See you in 45.
House医生 我们得赶快
Dr. House...We need to hurry.
是啊 赶快
Yeah,we need to hurry.
小小建议/村民乐队扮警察那套已经过时了
Little advice, I mean,obviously the village/people played out the whole cop thing.
拜托 中情局?
But,come on,CIA?
你真以为有人会相信?
Do you seriously expect/anyone to believe that?
有道具的时候就信了
It helps when you have props.
看着笔
Keep your eye on my pen.
很好
Very good.
在发作有恶心或呕吐么?
Any nausea or vomiting/before the seizure?
没有
no.
我爸倒是有 不过他在赛前一直如此
My dad had some,but he's/always like that before a race.
可能是食物中毒
It could have been food poisoning.
- 你们俩一起吃的早餐?/- 不是
- You two eat breakfast together?/- no.
有无坐骨神经痛或脊髓损伤病史
Any history of sCIAtica/or spinal injury?
没有
no.
深部肌腱反射异常
Abnormal deep tendon reflex.
确定?
Really?
让我看看
Let me see.
- 有反射/- 不是没有 我说异常
- It's there./- I didn't say it wasn't there.I said it was abnormal.
我们给你做一个MRI来确诊
We're gonna give you an mri to be sure,
不过我猜 是脱水和中暑造成的
but I'm guessing your symptoms were/caused by just dehydration and the heat.
你猜?
You're guessing?
听着 我靠一小时开300英里谋生
Look,I make a living/driving 300 miles an hour,
所以保持清醒很重要
which makes the ability to stay/conscious kind of important.
我肯定这是中暑
I'm sure it's just heatstroke.
但是我们要做MRI来保证万无一失
But we're gonna do an/mri to be extra careful.
你说你把手机放办公室了
you said you left your/cell in your office.
我撒谎了
I lied.
我不打算没收你的手机
I wasn't going to take it,
只想告诉你起飞的时候关机
just tell you to turn/it off for takeoff.
我知道 只想看看你能不能辨别我在说谎
I know...just wanted to see if/you could tell that I was lying.
这是有用的信息
Useful information.
- 什么?/- 你在哪
- Yeah?/- Where are you?
执行中情局的高度机密任务
I'm on a top-secret/mission for the CIA.
好 你的赛车手什么毛病都没有
Right.There was nothing on/your racecar driver's ct,
CT和病史以及身体检查都正常
and the history and/physical were normal.
我觉得她的深部肌腱反射有点异常
Her deep tendon reflexes/seemed a bit weak to me.
无反射可能是Miller-Fisher综合症
Areflexia could mean miller fisher.
对 无反射可能是Miller-Fisher综合症
Yes,areflexia could mean miller fisher,
可反射是微弱 而非全无
but since the reflex/was weak,not absent,
依据不足 我准她出院了
it doesn't mean/anything.I'm releasing her.
- 你可以继续打扑克了/- 扑克是违法的
- You can go back to your poker game./- Poker's illegal.
中情局不会允许违法活动
CIA would never allow illegal activity.
会是Miller-Fisher综合症吗?
Have you considered miller fisher?
怎么了
Why? What happened?
她刚刚又发作了一次
She just had another seizure.
她现在是垂直性眼球震颤
And now she's getting/a vertical nystagmus.
我们认为是Miller-Fisher综合症
We think it's miller fisher,
是发炎性疾病
an inflammatory process.
罕见情况下 可能导致呼吸衰竭 但...
In rare cases,it can cause/respiratory failure,but...
等等 她可能无法呼吸?
Wait,she could stop breathing?
你说我没什么病 你说你很确定
You said there was nothing/wrong.You said you were sure.
你刚刚又发作了一次 显然你是有病
You just had another/seizure.Clearly,there's something wrong.
为什么我要相信你能治好我?
So why should I trust you/to figure out what it is?
House医生在哪? 我到这家医院来就是...
Where's Dr. House?I'm/at this hospital bec...
没事的
It's gonna be all right.
进行血浆置换
We just need to start/the plasmapheresis.
不
no!
不会没事的
It's not going to be all right,
你显然不知道你在干什么
because you obviously don't/have a clue what you're doing.
我不让你碰我
I'm not letting you touch me.
- 宝贝 别这样/- 我要见House医生
- Honey,come on./- I wanna see House!
他在哪
Where is he?
反恐24小时里可比这气派
Looks a lot better on24.
我收回刚刚的话
I take that back.
我是Samira Terzi医生
Dr. Samira terzi.
很荣幸见到你 House医生
It's a pleasure to meet you,dr. House.
真的很感谢你在匆忙中赶来会诊
We really appreCIAte the/consult on such short notice.
没什么比帮助同僚更荣幸的了
There's nothing that gives me more/pleasure than helping out a colleague.
这是梅奥医疗中心的Sidney Curtis医生
This is Dr. Sidney curtis/from the mayo clinic.
他也来帮助诊断
He's also agreed to/help with the diagnosis.
- House医生/- 免疫学家Sidney Curtis?
- Dr. House./- curtis on immunology sidney curtis?
你读过我写的书 ?
Oh,you've read it?
没有 那书垫钢琴脚正好
Nope! But it is keeping my piano level.
"蛇蝎女"来电
"Cutthroat Bitch"
可怜的病人在哪?
So...where is the poor,sick fella?
- 我们怎么办?/- 我也不知道
- What do we do?/- I don't know yet.
- 她需要治疗/- 这是测试 对吧?
- She needs treatment./- This is a test,right?
你会把我们的一举一动向他汇报
You're reporting back/to him everything we do.
是啊 我还叫病人故意不合作
Yeah.And I asked the/patient to be uncooperative.
个人感觉 她也演得太过火了
Personally,I think she overplayed it.
你让我们显得像白痴 她才不合作的
She's being uncooperative because/you made us all look like idiots.
要是没办法让她同意治疗
We're only gonna look like idiots/if we can't figure out how to get her
那才叫白痴
to agree to the treatment.
要是House 他会怎么做
What would House do right now?
嗑点药 羞辱我们 然后骗病人
Pop a pill,insult/us,and trick the patient.
最后一项 我们也能做到
We can do that last part.
她从没见过House 对吧? 谁有拐杖
She's never met House/before,has she?Who's got a cane?
House不在这里
House isn't here.
我们也不能装他
We're not gonna act like him.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我...
I,uh...
我要做很多医生都不会做的事情
I'm gonna do what doctors/aren't supposed to do:
承认犯了错
admit I made a mistake.
我没有自己分析你的症状
I shouldn't have been so/quick to dismiss your symptoms.
但你确实需要马上开始血浆置换
But you need to let us/start the plasmapheresis.
你想干什么
What do you want?
Case?
宝贝 你清醒么?
Honey,do you know where you are?
她在发烧
She's burning up.
- 开始治疗/- 不行
- Start the treatment./- We can't.
- 你有我的同意 她已经神志不清了/- 来不及了
- You've got my permission.She's obviously confused./- It doesn't matter anymore.
Miller-Fisher症不会导致妄语和发烧
Miller fisher doesn't/cause delirium and fever.
我也不知道这是什么病
I don't know what this is.
不能完整透露他的病历
I'm afraid there are going to be some/limitations on his medical history.
需要知道什么 我尽力提供
Just let me know what you need,and/I should be able to provide it.
我的医疗责任保险 不包括解剖外星人
Fyi,my malpractice insurance/doesn't cover alien autopsies.
没关系 X档案小组就在隔壁
That's fine. X- files are the next wing over.
第一次感觉发病时 他人在哪里?
Where was the patient/when he first felt ill?
抱歉 这是机密信息
Sorry,that's classified.
能透露的是 世界上绝大多数地方/John都去过
But assume there aren't too many/places in the world john hasn't been.
对 John是化名
And,yes,john's a cover name.
你由什么断定他是被谋害的?
And what makes you think it/was an attempt on his life?
抱歉 这也不能告诉你
Sorry,can't tell you that either.
你能告诉我们什么?
What can you tell us?
Oswald和玛丽莲·梦露睡过吗?/(Oswald 刺杀肯尼迪的凶手)
did oswald really have/sex with marilyn monroe?
老天啊
Good lord.
真是专业
Very professional.
五天前 他重185磅
Five days ago,he was 185 pounds.
非常健康
Perfect health.
酷
Cool.
发烧和妄语能排除...
Fever and delirium rule out...
他不会因为你打了多少电话就雇用你
Uh,he's not gonna hire you just/because you call him the most.
尤其是他不想接电话的时候
EspeCIAlly since it's obvious/he doesn't wanna be called.
症状排除了Miller-Fisher症/多发性硬化症更符合
Symptoms rule out miller/fisher.M.s. Fits better.
恶化太快 更像是脑膜炎
Progression's too/fast.More likely meningitis.
无反射不符合...
Areflexia doesn't fit as well with...
- 淀粉样变性症说得通/- 那比多发性硬化发展还慢 是狼疮
- Does with amyloidosis./- That's even slower than m.s.It's lupus.
这次我同意小男人
I'm with the little man on this one.
攻击身体和大脑 显然是自体免疫疾病
It's attacking the body and/the brain.Classic autoimmune.
要调情尽管来 不过我得警告你
Flirt all you want,but/I should warn you:
我只对犹太姑娘动真情
shiksas are for practice.
狼疮很凶猛 不会漏掉肾脏
Lupus this aggressive/wouldn't spare her kidneys.
这是神经性的
It's primarily neurological.
- 给她用.../- 她的MRI没有发现硬化斑
- Let's start her on/- Why no plaques on her mri?
MRI不一定准确
Mri was inconclusive.
- 我不认为/- 你又确定是多发性硬化症
- So I don't know/- So now you're sure that it's m.s.
就像你一会儿确信是中暑/一会儿又确定是Miller-Fisher症一样
Just like you were sure it was miller fisher/an hour after you were sure it was heatstroke.
症状符合 给她用干扰素
The symptoms fit.Start/her on interferon.
听你差遣 House不会给我们加分
We're not gonna score any points with House/if we solve this just by running your errands.
- 我知道你们想找到正确答案/- 你不想?
- I get that you want to be right./- You don't?
我只想治病救人 而不是从上司那得分
I'm just trying to save a/patient,not score points with my boss.
让我们做些检查也无妨?
Would it hurt the patient/if you let us run some tests?
给你们三个小时
You've got three hours.
我们做了6遍完整的毒素筛检
We've run six complete tox screens,
所有的重金属 毒物 生物战剂/能想到的都做了
tested for every heavy metal,poison,and/biological agent we can think of.
这里说他吃了很多栗子
It says here he ate a lot of chestnuts.
等等
Hold on a second.
如果松鼠解放军也来凑热闹 我可不干了
If the squirrel liberation/army's involved,I'm outta here.
- 那些啮齿小动物可/- 七叶树果是有毒的
- Those little rodents are/- Horse chestnuts are poisonous.
- 如果弄错了/- 七叶树果可能长得像栗子
- If someone switched them/- Horse chestnuts may look like chestnuts,
但比马脚上的茧子还难吃
but they taste like a/horse's lower-than-chestnuts.
他无意识吃下几百颗的可能性/微乎其微
Which makes the theory that he accidentally ate/a couple of hundred slightly less persuasive.
他是潜伏在...德黑兰的后巷
And seeing as how he was prowling/the back alleys of...tehran?
不是德黑兰 是...
It wasn't tehran.It was..
一不小心 差点漏嘴了
oops.You almost got me.
一定得知道当地环境因素
Unless we know the local/environmental factors...
- 有毒植物啦/- 你知道我不能说
- Poisonous flora/- You know I can't tell you that.
那还要我们在这干嘛/你去GOOGLE上查毒药不就好了
Well,then,why are we here?You/might as well just google "poison."
他们告诉我的就是...
All they would tell me is...
他最后在玻利维亚呆了9个月
He spent the last 11 months in bolivia.
去玻利维亚要杀谁?
Who you gonna kill in bolivia?
- 我的旧管家?/- 我们不杀人
- My old Housekeeper?/- We don't kill people.
抱歉 你们要边缘化谁?
I'm sorry.Who are you gonna marginalize?
如果是去杀我管家 她确实该死
If it is my Housekeeper,she/has it coming.
谁让她擦窗户不擦两面/你说我有理还是没错?
Cleaning the windows means cleaning/both sides.Am I right,or am I right?
他做什么有紧要呢?
What does it matter what he was doing?
- 这人快死了/- 不会的
- The guy's dying./- Not anymore.
我知道是什么 是谁在毒害他
I know what's poisoning him.And who.
John/(澳大利亚人代称"啤酒")
John.
是胰腺炎罢了
It's just pancreatitis.
他不是酒鬼
He's not an alcoholic.
还有 除非他的胰腺长在手指上
And unless his pancreas/is in his fingers...
特工就不会感染真菌了吗?
Spies can't get fungal infections?
- 皮肤上的烧伤呢?/- 特工不会晒伤吗?
- And the burns on his skin?/- Spies can't get sunburns?
玻利维亚没太阳吗?
Bolivia doesn't have sun?
要么相信他的理论/病人是个不喝酒的醉汉
So,either we go with his theory/of the non-drinking drunk,
要么认为他是被下毒了/手法高明 无迹可寻
or he was poisoned by some group with the/resources to make it completely untraceable.
比如用某种同位素
Some customized isotope.
治疗放射物中毒
Let's treat for radiation poisoning.
碘保护你的甲状腺
The iodine's to protect your thyroid.
抗生素治疗感染
Antibiotics are to handle infections.
过几个小时就起效了
Should start working/in a couple of hours.
该庆祝一下
We should celebrate...
干上一杯 或是喝个痛快
With a beer.Or eight.
我不饮酒
I don't drink.
否认得太干脆 一定有鬼
Oh...me thinks he doth protest too much.
他病得快死了 还需要隐瞒喝酒吗?
He's deathly ill.Why would/he lie about drinking?
杀人的负罪感
Guilt over killing a man.
会让任何人染上酒瘾
Make anyone hit the sauce.
- 我们不杀人/- 对
- We don't kill people./- Right.
你只是对家人和朋友说谎
You just lie to your friends and family,
弄个假身份 引诱别人背叛祖国
establish false identies,trick/people into betraying their country.
他从来不掩饰自己喝酒/他太诚实了
He'd never cover up his/drinking-- he's too honest.
有些事情 我一直想知道
Hey. Something I've/always wanted to know.
Ginger涂上有毒的口红吻Gilligan/(CBS电视剧 盖里甘的岛)
That poison lipstick that/ginger used to kiss gilligan...
为什么她没有死?
Why didn't that kill her?
关键时刻
Okay,drum roll.
腰椎穿刺显示不是脑膜炎
Lp is negative for meningitis.
Cole 不好意思
Sorry,cole.
脂肪垫活组织切片结果是...
Fat pad biopsy is...
哦 等等
Oh,wait for it...
不是淀粉样变性病 13号错了
Negative for amyloidosis.And/thirteen goes down.
- 可以加快进度吗? 我儿子.../- 我能有个孩子吗 我工作太努力了
- Could we hurry this up?My son has/- Can I have a kid too?I'm working too hard.
这我可以帮你
I could hook you up.
如果我有两分钟空闲 还有止吐药/就让你试试
If I had two minutes and some/anti-nausea meds,i'd take you up on that.
金奖得主...
And for the gold...
蛋白质65 葡萄糖70
Protein 65,glucose 70.
多发性硬化 用干扰素
It's m.s.Start her on interferon.
翻到最后一页 红细胞沉降率是95/抗核抗体有轻微阳性反应
Turn to the last page Sed rate's/95.A.n.a.'s weakly positive.
- 阳性? 是狼疮/- 轻微的 不是狼疮 是多发性硬化
- Positive? It's lupus./- Weakly.Not lupus,it's m.s.
不能肯定是哪个 两样都治
We obviously don't know/what it is.Treat for both.
不 让你们化验 我已经让步了
No. I gave in on the test.
不准按两种完全不同的诊断医治她
I'm not treating her for two/completely separate diseases
你认为狼疮能让你得到嘉奖
because you think lupus/will win you a prize.
- 还认为是狼疮吗?/- 当然
- Still think it's lupus?/- Yeah.
我也这么认为
Me too.
出了紧急事件 得去急救室求助
In case of emergency,go/to the emergency room.
- 可能是狼疮/- 我们也这么认为
Could be lupus.That's what we figured.
- 你们来这里干什么?/- 你是免疫学专家 需要你来确认
- Then why are you here?/- You're an immunologist.We wanted to confirm
你想要我帮你们陷害谁?
Who are you looking for me to/help you sell down the river?
House还是Cuddy?
House or cuddy?
Foreman
Foreman.
- 帮不了/- 他坚持是多发性硬化
- Sorry./- He's pushing m.s.
他当了管事的/就非要证明自己是最聪明的
Thinks that because he's in charge,he has/to prove he's the smartest guy in the room.
关于你的传闻/都说你视病人利益高于一切
All I've heard about you: you put/the patient above everything else.
这也是你不讨人喜欢之处
That's why everyone/finds you so annoying.
House只在意结果
All House cares about is results.
我知道 我们是想对付Foreman
I know. I'm talking about/how to do deal with Foreman.
我也一样
So am i.
高烧温度降到了华氏101.5/(摄氏38.6)
Fever's down to 101.5.
治疗起效了 为什么把我叫出来
Treatment's working.Why are we out here?
找出那种治疗产生了作用
Trying to figure out/which treatment's working.
在病人面前讨论有点失礼
It's kind of tacky doing/it in front of the patient.
你也给她用了类固醇?
You put her on steroids too?
我们没办法 红细胞沉降率表明是狼疮
We had no choice...The/sed rate pointed to lupus.
抗核抗体说明了不是
And the a.n.a.Ruled it out!
医生
Doctors!
腿痛吗?
Legs hurt?
我感觉不到腿 动不了了
I can't feel them at all.I/don't think I can move them.
生命体征稳定了
Vitals stabilizing.
胃部的不适也消失了
Tummy ache's gone as well.
治疗起效了
So the treatment's working.
想要摆脱扫兴的老头医生/跳上公司的喷气机
Wanna ditch Dr. Killjoy/and...hop in the company jet?
去往墨西哥短途旅行?
Little trip down mexico way.
我说的不是国家和飞机
And I'm not talking about/the country or the plane.
你认为装疯卖傻 大谈性爱/会让女孩动心?
Do you think acting like an idiot/and talking about sex works on girls?
要是没用 人类早灭绝了
Well,if it didn't,the human race/would have died out long ago.
有蹊跷/某人的胰腺炎理论被证实是错误的
You're pretty cheery for/someone who was just proved wrong
可你还是兴致勃勃
about his pancreatitis theory.
我被证实是正确的/这点兴致勃勃 程度刚刚好
I'm appropriately cheery for/someone who's being proved right.
John已经近六小时未呕吐了
John hasn't vomited in six hours.
能吐什么? 我把他的午餐都吃了
What's to vomit?I'm eating his lunch.
不供给营养是治疗胰腺炎的方法
Withholding nutrients is the/treatment for pancreatitis.
与你给他的抗生素药一起作用
That and the antibiotics you put him on.
不过我取下了碘溶液输液袋
I did unhook your iodine,though.
我是不是把你们玩得团团转?
Didn't seem to fit with the whole/I'm-just-jerking- You-guys-around gestalt.
你太过分了
You're unbelievable.
问问John是愿意诚实但是病重/还是撒了谎但病治好了
Well,let's ask john if he'd rather/be sick honestly or cured dishonestly.
John
John.
有没有可能他只是...
Any chance he's just...
被感激冲昏了头脑?
Overwhelmed with gratitude?
瘫痪
Paralysis.
嗯 这是新的症状?
Uh...It's a new symptom?
为什么不写在白板上
Big white space on the/board where it would fit?
用漂亮的 各种颜色的记号笔
Nice,multicolored markers?
我不写是因为不确定这是真实的症状
I'm not writing it because we/can't know if it's a real symptom.
因为这两家伙失控了 给她注射类固醇
When these two went rogue and/pumped her full of steroids--
类固醇不会造成瘫痪
Steroids don't cause paralysis.
她同时在用干扰素
She was also on interferon!
同时给药会毁了免疫系统
Giving her both probably/fried her immune system.
天知道会引起什么的感染呢
Who knows what infection/you could cause--
我们咨询了免疫学家
We consulted an immunologist.
- 她说我们.../- 她?
- She said we have/- She?
你是说Cameron医生?
You talking about dr. Cameron?
- 她说狼疮.../- 她让你们治疗
- She thought lupus was/- She tell you to start treating?
是的 他们无视你 他们搞砸了
Yes,they've ignored you.They screwed up.
看你斥责他们可真有趣
And it's fun watching you spank them.
但 回到医学讨论上来行吗?
But can we get back to the medicine?
你们最不在乎的就是医学
The last thing any of you give/a damn about is the medicine!
瞧...
Look...
我不是说你们是坏医生或者人品有问题
I'm not saying you're/bad doctors or bad people.
但是House是
But House is.
他制造了一个人吃人的世界
He created a nasty/little cutthroat world,
把你们安排于其中 看你们明争暗斗
planted you in it,and/is watching you play.
除了他有乐子 谁都占不到好处
And none of it works/for anyone except him.
谁赢都一样
And whoever wins.
考虑到病情恶化速度之快/很可能是肉毒杆菌中毒
Given its quick progression,we/gotta assume botulism.
我去她家 检查她的冰箱和食品储藏室
I'll go to her place,check/out her fridge and pantry.
不是肉毒杆菌中毒 是脊髓灰质炎
It's not botulism.It's polio.
天才 该搜查她家 找找看有没有/罗斯福的遗骨或时间机器
Brilliant.We should search her home/for fdr's remains or a time machine.
她可能因接触了去过非洲的人 而感染
She could have contracted it from/anyone who's been to africa or...
她有接种疫苗
She's been vaccinated.
疫苗会失去作用...
Vaccines wear off.
20多年了 美国没有发现一则病例
There hasn't been a single/american case in over 20 years.
我见过这病
I've seen this disease.
- 我知道是什么样的病情/- 所以你才觉得是
- I know what it looks like./- That's why you're finding it
因为你在找这个病
Because you're looking for it.
脊髓灰质炎 太疯狂了
Polio...it's crazy.
House不会这么认为的
House wouldn't think so.
那去找House 告诉他你的理论
So go find House and/tell him your theory.
找个私人时间 我说真的
Take a personal day.Seriously.
离开这里
Get outta here.
你没有权利炒我
You don't have the power to fire me.
但我有权利将你逐出我的病例
But I do have the power to/kick your ass off my case.
开始治疗肉毒杆菌中毒
We're starting the botulism treatment.
剩下的人 去找证明
The rest of you,look for confirmation.
- 他应该被起诉/- 好啦 放轻松
- He should be brought up on charges./- Okay,relax.
我会把你的书从钢琴脚下拿走
I'll take your book/out from under my piano.
他会因放射病而死
He's dying of radiation sickness.
显然他在经受折磨
He's obviously in pain.
如果你不横加干涉 这一切本可以避免
All of which could have been avoided/if you hadn't interfered with...
你这是干什么
What was that for?!
放射病在特定的时间杀死特定的细胞
Radiation sickness kills/specific cells at specific times.
在他痛不欲生前 头发应该成把地掉下
His hair should be coming out in/clumps before he's writhing in pain.
既然没有 我知道是什么伤害他了
Since it's not,I know/who's trying to kill him.
上帝
God.
是血癌 华氏巨球蛋白血症
It's blood cancer.Waldenstrom's.
辐射引发感染 会导致
Radiation can cause/infections,which set off--
如果有切实的证明是谋杀
If had any real evidence of foul play,
你们会去拷问玻利维亚人/而不是逼我来这里 欲火焚身
you'd be torturing bolivians instead of putting/me into a state of anticipatory sexual arousal.
- 可以两样都治吗?/- 真烂的想法
- Can we treat for both?/- Bad idea.
除非你就是那个要毒他的人
Unless you're the one/who's trying to poison him.
我去安排血浆置换和化疗
I'll arrange for/plasmapheresis and chemo.
在他做了这一切之后/你还相信他?
Are you gonna trust/him after what he did?
我虽不信任他 但同意他的观点
I don't have to trust/him to agree with him.
你说得有道理
You make a good point.
我尽犯错 但是她还是不听你的
I've been wrong every time,and/she still won't listen to you.
要么她真的喜欢我/要么就是真的讨厌你
So either she really likes/me or she really hates you.
我可是乘喷气机来的
And I got a ride in the jet.
嗨
Oh. Hi.
- 你在这里做什么/- 过来说嗨
- What are you doing here?/- Just came to say hi.
嗨 再说一次
Hi again.
Bearman女士哪去了?
Where's...mrs. Bearman?
- 把她送回家了/- 我预定好给她做磁共振血管成像
- Sent her home./- I was scheduling her for an mra.
如果给每个头痛病人都做/磁共振血管成像...
If we gave mras to every/patient with a headache--
不只是头痛/是她经历过最疼痛的一次
This wasn't just a headache,it/was the worst in her life.
你太幸运了 因为我是神经学家
Then lucky for you I'm a neurologist.
她去参加酒和奶酪品尝会了
She went to a wine and cheese tasting.
- 都能引发偏头痛/- 她没有偏头痛病史
- Both triggers for migraines./- She's never had a migraine before.
我第一次吃面包圈前 也没吃过面包圈
And I never hagel before/the first time I had one.
面包圈吃不死人
Bagels don't kill people.
典型的脑动脉定时炸弹
This is a classic/ticking-bomb aneurysm.
你给我上了一课
This taught me a lesson.
我想干预别的医生治疗病人时
I guess when I mess with/other people's patients,
我就像一个多管闲事的婊子
I risk looking like an officious bitch.
我们得找到Bearman女士
We're gonna have to/track down mrs. Bearman.
等等
Wait...
不用了
Never mind.
- 真好笑/- 这不好笑 完全是不成熟的表现
- That's funny./- It's not funny.It's totally immature.
是很好笑 不好笑是因为你是受害者
It is funny.You just can't appreCIAte/it because you're the victim.
因为提供会诊意见 我该受到羞辱和嘲笑
Yeah,I deserve shame and/ridicule for offering a consult.
做医生以来还从没听到过
Unheard of for a doctor.
你不是给予医学建议
You didn't offer a medical consult.
- 你提供的是 对付Foreman良策/- 为了病人啊
- You offered a "dealing with Foreman" consult./- For the good of the patient.
是House也会做的
It's what House would have done.
也许House听到了 会骄傲地留下热泪
Maybe House will hear about/it and tear up with pride.
你认为我是做给他看
You think I'm trying to impress him.
我想是的 你已经不是他的下属了
I think that,for someone/who's not involved in his team,
可你还纠缠在他的团队里
you're remarkably involved in his team.
随它去吧
Let it go.
随他去吧
Let him go.
这就是成熟的表现了?
And that's mature?
血压120/80 让他休息吧
120 over 80.Let 'er rip.
现在医学上的障碍也消除了
Now we got the medical/stuff out of the way.
何不去你家
Why don't we meet back at your place
训练下审问技巧呢
for some enhanced/interrogation techniques?
暗号是 "救命 求求 求求你 停下来"
My safe word/is,"help,please,please stop."
两个"求求"
It's two pleases.
如果发现有少 你就继续 别停下
Anything less than that,you keep going.
你若治好了此人/我就给你看我私人的水板
You actually cure this guy,i'll/show you my private water board.
需要向肿瘤学家征询下化疗
We need to consult an/oncologist about the chemo.
哦 不好意思 我以为...
Oh,I'm sorry,I thought...
你还在暗示
You were still euphemizing.
我的男仆懂点肿瘤学
My valet knows a little oncology.
我在想你什么时候能成熟些/厌倦回避接我的电话
I was wondering when you'd/grow bored of avoiding my calls.
我绝不会对无视你感到困倦
Oh,I can never grow/bored of ignoring you.
治疗华氏白血病最新的方案是?
What's the latest/protocol on waldenstrom's?
- 你在哪里?/- 中情局总部
- Where are you?/- CIA headquarters
氟阿糖腺苷的用量...
How much/fludarabine--
你现在 要么是磕完一瓶维柯丁/裸体瘫倒在地板上
Either you're sprawled/naked on your floor
要么磕完一瓶伟哥
with an empty bottle of/vicodin,or collapsed naked
赤裸着瘫在电脑前
in front of your computer/with an empty bottle of viagra.
告诉我是哪个/因为Chase又开了新注
Please tell me which,because/chase has another pool going.
他们用飞机接我来给一病人诊疗
They flew me in to help/deal with a sick employee.
- 多少剂量.../- 你有幻觉 该死的
- How much/- Hallucinations.Damn!
我不该赌你服了伟哥
I shouldn't have bet on the viagra.
好吧 打电话到兰利(CIA总部昵称)总机/然后拨分机
Okay,call the langley/switchboard,ask for extension...
- 3578/- 3578
- 3578./- 3578.
作为一个仆人 他得的太多了
He asked an awful lot/of questions for a valet.
我的小弟弟上恰好有空缺
You know,I happen to have a/position available on my penis.
等等... 我又说了个冷笑话
Wait a second-- I think/I screwed up that joke.
你给我份工作?
You offering me a job?
我很乐意
I'd settle for that.
做你的下属是很诱人
As tempting as a/position on your staff is,
- 但我喜欢这里/- 我的薪水高
- I like it here./- Pays better.
我们只处理了一起谋杀事件
And we've only had one/assassination attempt.
我确定你会是个好老板
And I'm sure you're a great boss.
所以你的手下几个月前集体出逃
That's why your fellows left/en masse a couple of months ago.
我有卫星监控
I have satellite images.
神探加杰特
Inspector gadget.
我的天啊 你真在中央情报局
My god.You're actually at the CIA.
你一定得来这地方
You've gotta get down here.
这里有卫星直接监控Cuddy的阴道
They've got a satellite aimed/directly into cuddy's vagina.
我告诉他们侵入的可能性几乎为零
I told them the chances of/invasion are slim to none,
华氏白血病
waldenstrom's.
推荐剂量是25毫克每平方米
Recommended dose is 25/milligrams per meter squared.
他们给你做了背景调查?
They do a background check on you?
25毫克
25 milligrams?
他们给你做了背景调查
They did a background check on you,
他们给你的朋友做了背景调查
they did a background/check on your friends.
放轻松
Relax.
我想他们已经知道你/从阿富汗带海洛因回来的事情了
I'm sure they already know that you/brought heroin back from afghanistan.
那...那不是真的 我没去过阿富汗
That...that's not true.I've/never been to afghanistan.
House?
- 她的情况恶化了吗?/- 体温上升了一点
- She's getting worse?/- Fever's risen slightly.
但绝对是 呃...
But it's definitely,um...
什么...肉毒杆菌中毒?
What...botulism?
对吧? 如果你再错一次
Right?Because if you're wrong again,
治疗她没生的病--
and you're treating her for/something she doesn't even have--
抗毒素还没来得及起作用呢
The antitoxin hasn't/had time to work yet.
我知道很难 不过还是耐心点
I know it's hard,but try to be patient.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我知道你气我打断
I know you're pissed I interrupted,
但下一秒后你会更生气
but you're gonna be even/more pissed in a second.
你不跟我说就给她做测试?
You tested her without telling me?
没错 我真的非常抱歉
Yeah. And I know,I'm/really,really sorry.
但...结果是阳性的
But...on the other hand,it's a positive.
她得了脊髓灰质炎
She has polio.
现在怎样 老板?
Now what,boss?
House在哪?
Where's House?
他放了门诊四小时鸽子
He's blown off four hours of clinic.
他为中情局做会诊
He's consulting for the CIA.
我说真的 打到langley 转分机35...
Seriously.Call langley/and ask for extension 35...
3536?
肯定有两个3的 我写下来了
There's definitely two threes.I/- I wrote it down.
- 我记在哪儿的/- 他必须双倍补偿逃岗的时间
- I have it somewhere./- He's gonna make up twice his skipped hours in the clinic.
好啊
Okeydoke.
你掩护他 罚你双倍于他的门诊时间
And for protecting him,you're/gonna make up twice that.
为什么罚我比对他还狠?
Why are you punishing me worse than him?
因为House不学乖 你还长点记性
Because House never learns.You might.
你觉得怎么样?
How are you feeling?
糟透了
Like crap.
是啊 癌症就是那样的
Yeah,cancer can be that way.
我的头发都掉了
My hair is falling out.
是因为化疗吗?
That the chemo?
不 这太快了
No,it's too quick.
那说明什么?
So what does it mean?
说明你没得癌症
It means you don't have cancer.
确实有人想害死你
Someone actually did try to kill you.
你顽固
You're stubborn.
- 你傲慢!/- 没必要大吼
- You're arrogant!/- There's no need to yell.
你有可能害死那个人
You may have cost that man his life.
他正在做放射病的治疗
He's getting the radiation treatment.
晚了24小时!
24 hours too late!
我觉得你不对的时候 可没朝你吼
I didn't yell at you when/I thought you were wrong.
- 我又没错!/- 这样没用
- I wasn't wrong!/- This isn't productive.
已经不可能有用了 太迟了
There is no productive.It's too late.
因为你没经验 判断力差
Because of your/inexperience,your poor judgment.
看不出这是个胆大包天的傻瓜!
And your failure to/recognize a reckless fool!
冬虫夏草
Cordyceps sinensis.
那是...提炼自寄生虫生真菌的草药疗法
It's,uh...it's an herbal treatment derived/from a parasitic fungus,comes from caterpillars.
和螯合二巯丙醇一起作用
Along with dimercaprol chelation,
已被证明可以减轻放射对骨髓损伤
it's been shown to mitigate bone/marrow damage from radiation poisoning.
在猴子上
In monkeys.
对不起 我固执而且傲慢
I'm sorry.I was stubborn and arrogant.
自我指责帮不了她
Self-recriminations won't help her.
没什么能帮她 她得了脊髓灰质炎
Nothing's gonna help/her.She's got polio.
没有治愈办法 但还可以治疗
There's no cure,but/there are treatments.
- 她快死了/- 是的
- She's dying./- Yeah.
任何死亡都是一场悲剧
Every death's a tragedy.
奇怪 当我和Amber搞砸了/病人奄奄一息时
Funny how you weren't so depressed
你没有那么沮丧
when she just dying because/me and Amber screwed up.
感谢挑明这点 我还以自我为中心
And I'm also self-centered.Thanks/for clarifying.
别忘了自我怜悯
Don't forget self-pitying.
维生素C
Vitamin c.
极高剂量 在50年代是实验性的治疗方案
Extremely high doses.It was experimental/treatment protocol in the '50s.
- 现在还没完成?/- 他们...没有资金了
- And they haven't finished yet?/- They...lost funding.
那是因为维生素C不可能治愈脊髓灰质炎
That's because there's no logical/reason vitamin c would cure polio.
有人觉得可能
Well,someone thought there was.
还有人认为黑人做农具非常拿手呢
Someone thought black people/made excellent farm implements.
我不想伤害谁
I'm not talking about hurting anyone.
不过想让她多喝些橘子汁
I just wanna force feed/her some orange juice.
要不要再搭配点培根和鸡蛋?
You wanna throw in some/bacon and eggs as well?
如果你今天吸取了什么教训的话
If there's anything you learn today,
应该是你也可能犯错
it's gotta be that you can be wrong.
John 你听得见吗?
John,can you hear me?
我们要给你用一种实验疗法
We're going to start you on/an experimental treatment.
茶?
Tea?
是中国草药
It's a chinese herb.
- 非常有效/- 我快死了 是吗?
- Which has been effective in/- I'm dying,aren't i?
可能
Probably.
我们要尝试一种实验疗法
We're gonna attempt an/experimental protocol.
- 新药?/- 旧的 维生素C
- A new drug?/- An old one.Vitamin c.
大剂量的维生素C能杀死脊髓灰质炎病毒/修复神经损伤
Ultra-high doses have been shown to destroy/the polio virus and heal nerve damage.
那她的腿就能动了
She could regain use of her legs.
不太可能
It's unlikely.
但我们会尝试 别放弃
But we're gonna try.Don't give up.
恶心的感觉...
Nausea's...
没那么厉害了
not as bad.
放射病有潜伏期
Radiation sickness has a latency period.
可能感觉刚好一点 就又恶化了
You'll get better before you get worse.
你想知道我究竟做过什么吗?
You wanna know what I/really did down there?
如果好玩的话
Only if it's interesting.
那儿的女人...
The women there...
在狂欢节她们...
During carnival they...
跳一种舞
They do this dance.
叫作恶魔之舞
They call it the devil dance.
不好玩
Not interesting.
40天 我跟着
I spent all 40 days with this
国防部长的随员
attache to the minister of defense.
她是最...
The most...
保守传统的女人
buttoned-down woman/you'd ever meet.You know?
除了她跳这种舞的时候
'cept when she did this dance.
她答应告诉我一些事...
She agreed to tell me stuff...
这半截故事还算有趣
Okay,we have half a good story there.
因果报应
Karma.
摆脱负罪感最好的办法就是忏悔罪行
Best way to rid yourself of that/guilt is to confess your sins.
这疼痛是...对的
This pain is...right.
是种宽慰
It's comforting.
让我觉得...某种程度上 万物皆有因果
It makes me think/that...Somehow,it all makes sense.
为什么是40天?
What do you mean,40 days?
是他们发现
When they found out.
她告诉了我机密的时候
What she...told me.
玻利维亚的狂欢节只有8天
Carnival in bolivia's only eight days.
你知道栗子长什么样吗?
You have any idea what/a chestnut looks like?
你这白痴
You idiot.
你说谁是白痴?
Who are you calling an idiot?
那些知道John在巴西活动/而不是玻利维亚的人
Whoever knew that john/was stationed in brazil,
- 巴西?
- not bolivia./- Brazil?
我猜该叫你白痴
Well,then,I guess I'm/talking to you,idiot.
那在同一地区
It's the same region.
是同种寄生物 同样的病
It's the same parasite,same diseases.
但不是同种语言
But not the same language.
在玻利维亚 栗子是栗子
In bolivia,chestnuts are chestnuts.
然而巴西是hascastanhas-do-para
Brazil,on the other/hand,hascastanhas-do-para,
字面意思是 "来自帕拉树的栗子"
literally,"chestnuts from para."
因为没有巴西人会笨到叫它们
Because it would be stupid/for people from brazil
巴西坚果!
to call them brazil nuts!
就算他吃了巴西坚果 有什么大不了
So he ate brazil nuts.Big deal.
不 他吃了很多巴西坚果
No,he ate a lot of brazil nuts.
这重要得很 因为含硒
Which is a big deal,because/they contain selenium.
大量的硒会导致疲劳
Which,in high doses,causes fatigue,
呕吐 皮肤刺痒 指甲脱落 脱发
vomiting,skin irritation,discharge/from the fingernail beds,
听起来耳熟吗?
and hair loss.Any of/that sounding familiar?
你能治疗吗?
Can you treat it?
已经开始治了
We've already started.
治疗方法是螯合 和放射病一样
Treatment's chelation,same/as for radiation sickness.
唯一的区别是 治疗坚果中毒效果好得多
The only difference is it works/a lot better on nut poisoning.
那还有什么问题?
So what's the problem?
你真是个白痴
You're an idiot.
她为什么在抖?
Why is she shivering?
血清低钙是这个疗法的副作用
Low serum calcium is a side/effect of the treatment.
我可以给她补充钙
I can give her a calcium supplement.
我胳膊疼
My arm hurts.
只有滴注率高 治疗才会有效
Infusion rate has to remain/high for the treatment to work.
有效吗?
Is it working?
- 你感觉到了?/- 是的
- You feel that?/- Yeah.
疼
It hurts.
起效了
It's working.
太神奇了
This is fantastic.
在我手下你能学到很多东西
There's a lot you can/learn in my fellowship.
我可以教你一些 新的方法
A few new procedures I could teach you.
当然需要护士去做准备
Course,we'd need a nurse to prep.
我知道怎么动动拇指杀人
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
实际上 我在委婉地说上床的事
Actually,I was just trying to/make another euphemism for sex.
- 我也是/- 上帝啊
- So was i./- Oh,god.
你怎么能跟这个白痴调情?
How can you flirt with this idiot?
他一次又一次的对我们撒谎
He lied to us again and again.
他违反法律 道德规范--
He broke/laws,ethical codes--
我是对的
I was right.
不过侥幸撞对一次
That doesn't mean everything.
帮助良多
It means a lot.
Curtis医生
Dr. Curtis.
House医生
Dr. House.
感谢你们帮忙
AppreCIAte your help.
- 嘿/- 嘿
- Hey./- Hey.
那时...
When...
你快死了 你试图把病传染给我
when you were dying,you/tried to infect me.
因为你知道我会竭尽全力治你
Because you knew i'd fight for you
如果我以为自己也快死了
if I thought I was dying too.
现在提这个/是为了让我原谅你搅局我的病人?
You bringing this up now so I'll/forgive you for messing with my patient?
我很高兴换了工作
I'm happy I changed jobs.
但我知道 不再会有那种...
But I know I'll never/have that sort of...
- 兴奋的感觉/- 你怀念有人想要杀你?
- Excitement./- You Miss people trying to kill you?
不是
no.
我怀念...不惜一切做好工作的人
I miss...people doing whatever/it takes to get the job done.
我猜那就是我很难放弃这工作的原因
I guess that's why I'm/having trouble giving it up.
我不该帮他们搅你的局
I shouldn't have helped/them mess with your patient.
他们必须这么做
They had to screw with me.
我全错了
I've gotten everything wrong.
我不信
I don't believe it.
你不会...
You're not...
全都对
Gonna get everything right.
但你也不会"全"错
But you're never gonna/get everything wrong.
早上好!
Morning!
你前两天干嘛去了?
Uh,where have you/been the last two days?
- 睡过了/- 我们救了赛车手
- Overslept./- We saved speed racer.
她得了脊髓灰质炎
She had polio.
我们用维生素C治好了
We cured it with vitamin c.
对啊
Yeah.
我还曾经用奎宁水治好抑郁症
I cured depression/with tonic water once.
事实上 里面还有点杜松子酒
Actually,I think there/was some gin in it too.
6小时共150克剂量
150 grams over six hours.
- 有效/- 不 没用
- It worked./- No,it didn't.
我说过脊髓灰质炎不能治愈
I told you you can't cure polio.
说明她不是没痊愈就是根本没得这病
That means either she's not/cured or she never had it.
既然她康复出院了
Since she's walking out of here...
我查了她入院时抽的血
I tested her blood from admittance.
没有脊髓灰质炎病毒
no polio.
说明Brennan搞砸了检测
that means brennan/screwed up the lab tests.
或者你搞砸了
or you screwed up your lab tests.
肯定是你 她好转了
you must have.she got better.
那就是病情反复 或间歇发作
so it's relapsing and remitting.
也许是...卟啉病
maybe...porphyria.
那有点牵强
nah,that's a stretch.
如果她得了卟啉病 尿是紫色的
if she had porphyria,you/would have seen purple urine.
你觉得他治愈了脊髓灰质炎可能性更大?
you think it's more/likely he cured polio?
他们相信
they believe it.
她的症状完全符合
her symptoms fit perfectly.
而另一种解释太复杂曲折
and the alternative is/unbelievably convoluted.
某些医生用安定下毒
some doctor would have/to poison her with valium
看起来就像脊髓灰质炎的症状/再伪造检测结果
so it looks like/polio,then fake a lab test,
然后给她用维生素C 停止下毒
then give her vitamin/c and stop the poison
她就神奇地痊愈了
so she magically gets better.
这是可行的 对吧?
actually...it is kind of doable,right?
你怎么想?
so what do you think?
在你联系斯德哥尔摩之前/我们给她检测一下铊中毒 怎么样?
should we test her for thallium/before you contact stockholm?
你给她下毒?
you poisoned her?
其实 Foreman认为是中暑 才是正确的
the really shocking thing is that/Foreman was right about the heatstroke.
我亲眼见到过维生素C治愈脊髓灰质炎
vitamin c cures polio.I've seen it.
对...在什么丛林诊所
yeah...in some bush clinic.
你需要一例正规实验室里的/脊髓灰质炎病例
you need polio in a/place with a proper lab.
问题是有正规实验室的地方/没有脊髓灰质炎
the only problem is that places/with proper labs don't have polio.
那些只害死穷人的病
there is no money in finding cures
总是没有钱资助研究治疗方法
for diseases that only kill poor people.
这会让他们做研究
this will make them do research.
我是不是伪造了检测结果 重要吗?
and what do you care/if I faked a lab test
数千性命能够被挽救
if it saves a few thousand lives?
我非这么做不可
I did what I had to do.
这不就是你雇我们的原因?
isn't that what you hired us for?
所以我也不会炒你
which is why I'm not gonna fire you.
而让你辞职
you're gonna quit.
快点 走吧
go on,get out of here.
你就这么让他走了?
so you're just gonna let him go?
毫无疑问
absolutely.
在你叫警察前 我得让他走的越远越好
I'm gonna let him get as far away/as possible before you call the cops.
这家伙疯了
guy's a nut job.
我留谁管事呢?
who the hell did I leave in charge?
- Foreman./- 那么做自有道理
- Foreman./- there was a reason for that.
下次 听他的
next time,listen to him.
你去哪儿了?
where have you been?
- 别说是中情局/- 行
- and don't say the CIA./- okay.
顺便说一下 我的一个手下--
by the way,one/of my employees--
要么你让中情局的人打电话来证实你的故事
either you're gonna have/to get someone from the CIA
要么你做8小时门诊
to call and confirm your story,or/you're doing eight clinic hours
Wilson做16小时
and Wilson is doing 16.
我在Hamptons
I was in the hamptons.
帮一个玩对冲基金的富翁/治他儿子的鼻塞
I was helping some rich hedge/fund jerk treat his son's sniffles.
听起来很有趣吧
fascinating as that sounds.
看你这么诚实的份上 我饶了你的门诊时间
for your honesty,I/will forgiveyourhours.
谢谢
thank you.
才不!
no!
比给中情局帮忙更不可能的
the only thing less likely/than your helping the CIA
就是帮长岛富翁的忙
is your helping some/rich guy on long island.
你要完成你的门诊 还有Wilson的
you're doing your hours andWilson's.
我知道怎么动动拇指杀人
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
谁不呢?
who doesn't?
- 嗨/-嗨
- hi./- Hi
你的邀请 我准备接受
I'm going to take you up on your offer.
是吗?
yeah?
我住在几英里外
well,i,uh,I live a/couple miles from here.
我说的不是这个邀请
that's not the offer I meant.
我今天交了辞职信
I gave notice today.
你曾说你在公司里很开心
you said you were happy at the company.
我撒谎了 怕你用那个对付我
I lied.doubt you'll hold it against me.
周一早上九点见
i'll see you at 9:00 on monday.